drpsychmom.com 2015-12-29

# Privacy Policy - Dr. Psych Mom

Dr. Psych Mom is committed to respecting and protecting your online privacy.

This includes your need and your right to know what we do with the personal information you share with us. It also guides our policies regarding the management of this data, including how the information is collected, processed, and for what purposes.

“The Dr. Psych Mom website”: refers to the web pages. By accessing this website you are consenting to the way information is collected and used, as described within this privacy  and cookie policy.

In return, The Dr. Psych Mom website gives the commitment that we will use the personal data you provide only in ways that are compatible with the following privacy policy.

We may disclose non-personally identifiable aggregated user data, such as aggregated gender, age, height, weight, and usage data gathered from our tracker (without the inclusion of a user’s name or other identifying information) on the website, available to the public, for purposes of comparison and inspiration. We may also disclose this data to other third party organisations, approved by us, for research and commercial purposes.

Every time you visit our website your IP (Internet Protocol) address registers on our servers. Your IP address reveals no information other than the number assigned to you. We do not use this technology to get any personal data against your knowledge or free will (i.e., automatically recording e-mail addresses of visitors). Nor do we use it for any purpose other than to help us monitor traffic on our website, or (in case of criminal activity or misuse of our information) to cooperate with law enforcement.

If you log in to access your account and / or make comments, we will register these visits with the information you provided when you registered and as given to us by the third party login providers as detailed in the registration process. We reserve the right to use this information to moderate comments and access to commenting if needed. We will never sell your data, you won’t get spam because you have registered with us.

We use Akismet for comment moderation and to stop spam comments on our site. [Their privacy policy is here.](http://automattic.com/privacy/)

We have implemented Google Analytics features based on Display Advertising  ([Google Analytics Demographics and Interest Reporting](https://support.google.com/analytics/answer/2799357?hl=en)). You can [opt-out](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/) of Google Analytics for Display Advertising and customize Google Display Network ads using the Ads Settings. In addition, you can use the [Google Analytics Opt-Out Browser Add-on](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/) to disable tracking by Google Analytics. We will use the data provided by Google Analytics Demographics and Interest Reporting to develop the site and content around our users’ interests.

If you have any questions about our privacy policy, please [ask](http://www.drpsychmom.com/ask-dr-psych-mom-a-question/). Also, if you believe that any content on this website infringes on one or more of your copyrights, please [notify us](http://www.drpsychmom.com/ask-dr-psych-mom-a-question/).

## Cookies

We use a number of different cookies on our site. If you do not know what cookies are, or how to control or delete them, then we recommend you visit [http://www.aboutcookies.org](http://www.aboutcookies.org/) for detailed guidance.

The list below describe the cookies we use on this site and what we use them for. Currently we operate an ‘implied consent’ policy which means that we assume you are happy with this usage. If you are not happy, then you should either not use this site, or you should delete the cookies having visited the site, or you should browse the site using your browser’s anonymous usage setting (called “Incognito” in Chrome, “InPrivate” for Internet Explorer, “Private Browsing” in Firefox and Safari etc.)

Thanks for reading!
